wavs/1.wav|Professional life to producing Shakespeare's plays in a succession of theatre festivals in Ohio. As a result, my own childhood was awash in Elizabeth|0|0
wavs/2.wav|Verse. And although my dad poured most of his energy into rehearsals and performances, we usually had him to ourselves. At bedtime, he would read aloud to|0|0
wavs/3.wav|us from either the funny papers from a fat collection of stories called Tellers of Tales from Kipling's, The Jungle Book or best of all, from a series of|0|0
wavs/4.wav|Orange volumes for kids called Child-craft. One of the Child-craft books was a collection of poems. It mostly featured|0|0
wavs/5.wav|loopy verse by dog roll poets such as Edward Lear and Louis Carroll. None of the poems was especially complex or challenging, but we would request them|0|0
wavs/6.wav|over and over again. I can still rattle off several lines from memory. Once there was an elephant who tried to use the telephant|0|0
wavs/7.wav|I mean an elephant who tried to use the telephone or my favourite I never saw a purple cow. I never hoped to see one, but I can tell.|0|0
wavs/8.wav|anyhow, I'd rather see than be one. I remember my father's exact inflections his husky smell. The scratchy wool of our burnt orange couch.|0|0
wavs/9.wav|My father was a genial man, but slightly abstracted. He lived his life with his head halfway in the clouds. But when I and my SIBs.|0|0
wavs/10.wav|Cuddled up to him and listened to those poems. We were never closer. Those bedtime hours primed me for all the poetry I encountered later on in High|0|0
wavs/11.wav|school and college English classes. Nonsense verses gave way to the metaphysical poets, the cavalier poets, the romantic poets. Instead of telephone|0|0
wavs/12.wav|and purple cows. I discovered dunn Herrick Coleridge poem. I embraced these poets with a swoony, youthful exuberance. I felt|0|0
wavs/13.wav|as if they were speaking directly to me from centuries past. I remember declaiming Walt Whitman to my first girlfriend, pronouncing Marvels to his coy mistress.|0|0
wavs/14.wav|The perfect poem Memorizing keats'ode to autumn on a golden fall day in New England. As a student actor, I appeared in plays by T. S. Elliott.|0|0
wavs/15.wav|Dylan Thomas and William Butler Yates drunk with the power of their words. None of this made me an authority on poetry, nor even much.|0|0
wavs/16.wav|None of this made me an authority on poetry, nor even much of a scholar. But it made me a poetry lover, a lifelong seeker of poetic experience, whether reading, reciting or listening|0|0
wavs/17.wav|to great poems. I once witnessed firsthand just how intense the experience of poetry can be. The story bears repeat|0|0
wavs/18.wav|ing because it partly inspired this book. Ten years ago, a married couple asked me to host a benefit for a nonprofit organization they had founded|0|0
wavs/19.wav|in a town 80 miles from my home. The request came at a time when I was busy and overextended, so I hesitated. But when my wife told me that these people were good.|0|0
wavs/20.wav|See Paul Newman. I audition for a read for a part and he says that part is already cast. Dang.|0|0
wavs/21.wav|So Paul is going to be producer, director and star. And I said, well, you've got a big job ahead of you. And very happy. Very glad you let me come in.|0|0
wavs/22.wav|Do you see Nell Much's daughter? Yeah, because I knew her and I had met him before off Broadway things that we did there, so|0|0
wavs/23.wav|I leave and I'm at the elevator and he comes running down the hall and he said, Wait. Come back, come back, come back. Says I have another part. Maybe you would|0|0
wavs/24.wav|like to do. This guy's name is Simonowski? Yeah. This factory superintendent. One day shoot|0|0
wavs/25.wav|But it's like getting a job is like having money in your pocket. If you got it, you can get it, strangely enough. So this was in September. By October|0|0
